Where Peachtree Meets Sweet Auburn research files and interviews, 1991-1996
Emory University
Where Peachtree Meets Sweet Auburn research files and interviews, 1991-1996
Pomerantz, Gary M.
Manuscript Collection No. 890
13 linear ft. (26 boxes)
Research files of Gary Pomerantz for the publication of his book, Where Peachtree Meets Sweet Auburn: A Saga of Race and Family including audio recordings and transcripts of interviews that he conducted, research material, and manuscript drafts.
Emory University Manuscript, Archives, and Rare Book Library Pitts Theology Library
Source
Gift, 2001.
Restrictions on Access
Use copies have not been made for all of the audiovisual series at this time. Researchers must contact MARBL in advance for access to these materials.
Biographical Note
Gary M. Pomerantz is an award-winning journalist and author. After graduating from the University of California (Berkeley), Pomerantz joined The Washington Post as a sports reporter. In the 1990s, he moved to The Atlanta Journal-Constitution where he wrote feature stories, and penned columns and editorials. His first book was Where Peachtree Meets Sweet Auburn: A Saga of Race and Family (1996). It tells the story of race relations in 20th century Atlanta through the history of two families: the Allens and the Dobbs. Ivan Allen, Sr., the ambitious son of a Confederate cavalryman, moved to Atlanta from Dalton in 1895. Two years later, John Wesley Dobbs, the ambitious son of a slave, arrived in Atlanta from Cobb County. Over the course of the next two generations both of these families produced future mayors of Atlanta: Ivan Allen, Jr., who was the only southern politician to go to Washington, D.C. to speak in favor of the 1964 Civil Rights Act, and Maynard H. Jackson, the first African American mayor of a southern city. Where Peachtree Meets Sweet Auburn explores the origins and the workings of Atlanta's racial détente. It was named a "Notable Book of the Year" by The New York Times and it was included in The Georgia Center for the Book's "Georgia Top 25 Reading List." His other books include Nine Minutes, Twenty Seconds: A True Story of Tragedy & Triumph (2001) and Wilt, 1962: The Night of 100 Points and the Dawn of a New Era (2005).
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists of materials relating to Pomerantz's first book, Where Peachtree Meets Sweet Auburn: A Saga of Race and Family (New York: Scribner, c1996). It includes interviews, interview transcripts, research materials, notebooks and audiovisual materials relating to the history of the Allen and Dobbs families as well as the history of modern Atlanta. Of particular interest are the interviews and interview transcripts, which recount the racial, political, economic and social life of 20th century Atlanta.
Arrangement Note
Organized into four series: (1) Interview transcripts, (2) Research files, (3) Manuscript drafts, and (4) Audiovisual.
Selected Search Terms
Personal Names
Allen family.; Dobbs family.; Pomerantz, Gary M. Where Peachtree meets Sweet Auburn: the saga of two families and the making of Atlanta.
Topical Terms
African Americans--Georgia--Atlanta.
Geographic Names
Atlanta (Ga.)--Economic conditions--20th century.; Atlanta (Ga.)--Politics and government--20th century.; Atlanta (Ga.)--Race relations--20th century.; Atlanta (Ga.)--Social life and customs--20th century.
Form/Genre Terms
Interviews.; Sound recordings.
Occupation
Journalist.
Description of Series
- Interview transcripts, 1991-1995, Series 1; Boxes 1-5
  Scope and Content Note
  This series contains typed transcripts of some interviews Pomerantz conducted for the book. Where noted, the original audio cassettes are available in Subseries 3.1: Audio cassettes. It includes a diverse cross-section of Atlantans, including Allen and Dobbs family members, movers and shakers in the black and white business communities (T.M. Alexander, Sr. and Jr., W.L. Calloway, Larry Gellerstedt, Jr. and III, and Joel Goldberg), activists involved in the civil rights movement (Herschelle Sullivan Challenor and Donald Hollowell), journalists on both sides of the color line who covered this era (Paul E.X. Brown, W.L. Fowlkes, Aubrey Morris and Eugene Patterson), and influential political figures in Atlanta and Georgia (Michael Lomax, Herman Talmadge, Ernest Vandiver, and Andrew Young).
  Arrangement Note
  Organized in alphabetical order.
  - Acey, J. Earl and Port Scott, July 10, 1991. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, Cecil, June 14, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alexander, T.M., Sr., June 30, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen, Beaumont, September 23, 1991. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen, Inman, February 22, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Inman, November 3, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allen, Inman, August 2, 1995. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., July 30, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., November 12, 1991. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., February 6, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., July 17, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., September 3, 1992. [Cassettes available] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., May 7, 1993. [Cassettes available] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., September 9, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., March 14, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., May 23, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., July 28, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., December 20, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Allen, Ivan, III, Graveside Service, May 19, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Allen, Louise, November 29, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Allen, Louise, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Allen, Margaret P., September 20, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Allen, Margaret, August 23, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Arrington, Marvin, July 22, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Babbit, Joel, February 27, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Baranuik, Irene Dobbs, July 14, 1991. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Baranuik, Irene, June 11, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bennett, Francis, June 3, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Berry, George, October 4, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Blackburn, Willie Dobbs, July 7, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Paul E. X., August 29, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Buder, Imogene, April 9, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Butts, June Dobbs, November 24, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Calloway, W.L., June 23, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Campbell, Bill, August 7, 1995. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Carter, Constance Jackson, December 5, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Carter, Jimmy, March 18, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Challenor, Herschelle Sullivan, January 19, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Clement, Bill, Sr., December 29, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Clement, Bill, Jr., June 8, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Clement, Josephine, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Darnell, Emma, September 24, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dobbs, Mattiwilda, November 11, 1992. [Cassettes available] (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dobbs, Mattiwilda, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dodd, Marie, September 28, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Dodd, Marie, November 3, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Eaves, Reginald, November 11, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fowler, Wyche, August 15, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Fowlkes, William, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Franklin, David, September 14, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Franklin, David, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Franklin, Shirley, July 21, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fuster, Angelo, April 13, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Gellerstedt, Larry, Jr., March 22, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Gellerstedt, Larry, III, September 28, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Glenn, Jack, January 16, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Gloster, Hugh, September 29, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Goldberg, Joel, September 29, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Granger, Paula, February 9, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hammal, Tom, October 27, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Hill, Jesse, February 17, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hollowell, Donald, July 6, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Holmes, Bob, June 20, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Jackson, Brooke, April 5, 1995. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Jackson, Irene Dobbs, July 27, 1991. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Jackson, Irene Dobbs, July 27, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Jackson, Irene Dobbs, March 11, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Jackson, Irene Dobbs, May 2, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Jackson, Irene Dobbs, March 5, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr., September 9, 1991. [Cassettes available] (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr., February 23, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr., April 23, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr., May 25, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr., November 29, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr., February 14, 1995. [Cassette available] (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr., August 12, 1995. [Cassettes available] (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Jackson-Ransom, Bunnie, August 8, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Johnson, Leroy, September 12, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Leroy, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Jordan, Windsor, November 28, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Jordan, Windsor, February 16, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - King, Lonnie, May 21, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lomax, Michael, January 28, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Lomax, Michael, November 2, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Lowance, Mason, Jr., October 24, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Massell, Sam, August 18, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - McGill, Ralph, Jr., February 8, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - McQueen, Neal, June 23, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Carol Jackson, June 21, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Mitchell, Wade, July 14, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Morris, Aubrey, August 12, 1992. [Cassettes available] (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Morris, Jackie and John Head, May 17, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Patterson, Eugene, n.d. [Cassette available] (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Payne, Billy, August 10, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Pressley, Bill, November 18, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Royal, George, April 8, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Siddons, Anne Rivers, May 4, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Laura Maddox and Ed, April 22, 1993. [Cassette available] (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Speights, Deborah, March 10, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Talmadge, Herman, December 3, 1992. [Cassette available] (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Talmadge, Herman, August 18, 1994. [Cassette available] (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Thompson, Amanda & Knox, December 14, 1994 [Cassette available] (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Tuttle, Elbert, n.d. [Cassette available] (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Vandiver, Ernest, July 7, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Young, Andrew, July 24, 1995. [Cassette available] (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Research files, Series 2; Boxes 6-19
  The files include transcripts of shorter interviews, such as phone interviews, that were not taped, correspondence, newspaper and magazine clippings, archival research and biographical information. The family files contain genealogical information gathered from the U.S. census, legal records, obituaries and other sources. The five "Reporter's Notebooks" contain notes on a variety of individuals and subjects.
  Organized into three subseries: (2.1) Research files - Individuals, (2.2) Research files - Subject and (2.3) Reporter's notebooks.
  - Research files - Individuals, Subseries 2.1; Boxes 6-16
    - Abram, Morris (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Allen, Earnest (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Allen family (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Allen family (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Allen, Inman (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Allen, Isaac (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Allen, Isaac (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Allen, Ivan, Sr. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr. (1 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr. (2 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr. (3 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., Newspaper clippings (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., 1958 Governor's Race (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Allen, Ivan, III (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Allen, Ivan, III (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Allen, Ivan, IV (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Allen, Louise (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Allen, Margaret (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Allen, Robert (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Allen, Samuel (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Babbit, Joel (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Bond, Julian (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Borders, William Holmes (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Brown, H. Rap (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Bryans, Raleigh (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Butts, June D. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Carter, Connie J. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Clement, Bill (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Clement, Josephine (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Coleman, George (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Conklin, Meredith (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Cormier, Michel (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Dannals, Charles, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Darnell, Emma (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Dobbs, Balaam and Pleasant (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Dobbs family (1 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Dobbs family (2 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Dobbs family (3 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Dobbs family, Photographs (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Dobbs, Jesse L. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Dobbs, John Wesley (1 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Dobbs, John Wesley (2 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Dobbs, John Wesley (3 of 4) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Dobbs, John Wesley (4 of 4) (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Dobbs, John Wesley, Masonic letters (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Dobbs, John Wesley, Masonic letters (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Dobbs, Mattiwilda (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Dobbs, Minnie Hendricks (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Dobbs, Wesley and Judie (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Dodd, Marie (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Earnest, Peter (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Eaves, A. Reginald (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Eplan, Leon (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Ezell, Hank (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Fowler, Wyche (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Fuller, Chet (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Glassick, Charles (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Gloster, Hugh (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Goldberg, Joel (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Goodwin, George (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Haas, Bea (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Head, John (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Heyman, Joe (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Hill, Jesse, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Hodges, Beth Jackson (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Holder, Bob, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Holloway, Jenelsie Walden (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Hollowell, Donald (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Holmes, Robert A. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Horton, Jerry (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Howland, W. Slocum (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Hughes, Gail McAfee (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Jackson, Irene Dobbs (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Maynard H., Sr. (1 of 4) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Jackson, Maynard H., Sr. (2 of 4) (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Jackson, Maynard H., Sr. (3 of 4) (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Jackson, Maynard H., Sr. (4 of 4) (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr. (1 of 5) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr. (2 of 5) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr. (3 of 5) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr. (4 of 5) (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr. (5 of 5) (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Jackson, Maynard H., Jr., 1988-1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - James, Muriel (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Leroy (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Jones, E. Ladd (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Jordan, Bob (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Jordan, Dobbs (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Jordan, Vernon (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - King, Coretta Scott (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - King, Coretta Scott (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - King, Lonnie (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - McAfee, John M. (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - McAfee, John M. (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Research files - Subject, Subseries 2.2; Boxes 17-19
    - Allen Family, Lawsuits (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Allen Foundation, Inc. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Atlanta, 1980s (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Atlanta Chamber of Commerce, 1950s-1960s (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - [Atlanta] Olympic Bid (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Atlanta - Racial Turbulence, 1960s (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - "Atlanta Story," 1961, Pittsburgh Courier (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Auburn Avenue (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Central Atlanta Progress (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Citizens Trust [Bank] (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Cobb County and Kennesaw Mountain (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - "Community Leadership in the Atlanta NAACP, 1916-1936" (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - "Forward Atlanta" (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Georgia State Flag Debate (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Greeneville, Tennessee (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Greeneville, Tennessee Folks (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Ivan Allen Company Payroll and Family Stocks (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Marvin Griffin Collection, Bainbridge College (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Maynard Jackson [Jr.] Youth Foundation (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Middle Class Blacks in a White Society: Prince Hall Freemasonry in America (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Photo Releases (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Photo Releases (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Rodney King verdict [Violence in Atlanta after the Verdict] (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Sons of Confederate Veterans, John B. Gordon Camp, Ledger (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Sons of Confederate Veterans, John B. Gordon Camp, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - WSB-TV Collection (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Reporter's notebooks, Subseries 2.3; Box 19
    - Reporter's notebooks (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Manuscript drafts, Series 3; Box 20
  This series includes drafts of individual chapters as well as notes and timelines Pomerantz used to compose the chapters.
  Organized in chapter order.
  - Prologue (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 8 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 9 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 10 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 11 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 12 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 13 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 14 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 16 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 17 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 19 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 20 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 21 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 22 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 23 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Epilogue (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Audiovisual, 1991-1995, 1999, Series 4; Boxes 21-26, CD1-2
  The audiovisual series contains audio cassettes and two videotapes. The audiotapes consist primarily of interviews conducted by Pomerantz. Transcripts for many of these interviews can be found in Series 1: Interview Transcripts. The videotapes feature Ivan Allen, Jr. and Maynard H. Jackson, Jr. addressing the students in Pomerantz's Journalism class.
  Restrictions on Access
  Use copies have not been made for all of the audiovisual series at this time. Researchers must contact MARBL in advance for access to these materials.
  Organized into two subseries: (4.1) Audio cassettes and (4.2) Videotapes.
  - Audio cassettes, Subseries 4.1; Boxes 21-25
    - Aaron, Billye, January 5, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Acey, J. Earl and Port Scott, July 10, 1991 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Alexander, T.M., Sr., June 30, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Allen, Beau, September 23, 1991 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Allen, Beau, Tape 3, September 23, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Allen, Inman, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Allen, Inman, September 10, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Allen, Inman, August 2, 1995 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., November 12, 1991 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., February 6, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., July 17, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., Copy, July 17, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., Tape 1, September 3, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., Tape 2, September 3, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., Tape 3, September 3, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., October 27, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., Tape 1, May 7, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., Tape 2, May 7, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., September 9, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., December 20, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Allen, Ivan, Jr., n.d. (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Allen Tour, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Allen, Ivan, III, Graveside service (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Allen, Ivan, IV, February 22, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Allen, Louise, October 28, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Allen, Louise, November 29, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Allen, Margaret, September 20, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Allen, Margaret, August 23, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Baranuik, Irene, July 14, 1991 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Baranuik, Irene, Tape 1, June 11, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Baranuik, Irene, Tape 2, June 11, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Bennett, Frances, June 3, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Berry, George, October 4, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Blackburn, Willie Dobbs, July 7, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Borders, William H., August 8, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Brown, Paul E.X., August 29, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Buder, Imogene, April 9, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Butts, June [Dobbs], August 26, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Butts, June [Dobbs], "Phone" [interview], n.d. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Callaway, W.L., June 23, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Campbell, Bill, August 7, 1995 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Carter, Connie Jackson, Tape 1, December 5, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Carter, Connie Jackson, Tape 2, December 5, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Carter, Jimmy, March 18, 1993 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Clarke, Jim, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Clement, Bill, Sr., Tape 1, December 29, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Clement, Bill, Sr., Tape 2, December 29, 1994 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Clement, Bill, Jr., Tape 1, June 8, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Clement, Bill, Jr., Tape 2, June 8, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Clement, Bill, Jr. Tape 1, Copy, June 8, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Clement, Bill, Jr., Tape 2, Copy, June 8, 1992 [Transcript available] (Box 22, Folder 15)